put down some liquid latex let it dry
and then add little dots to the center
let that dry and after that go and put
scar wax on the bottom and also the top
of this
from there go and blend the edges press
down and pull the scar wax along with
also blend it with petroleum jelly and
then wipe off any extra pull out the
edges of the scar wax to go and make it
look jagged
and then follow along at the edges with
black cosmetic along with also a little
bit in the center go and follow this up
with red cosmetic and blend both the
black and red and then follow around the
edges with a small amount of black
cosmetic again
in the center use yellow cosmetic blend
that out slightly
and after that followed up with a
powdered red cosmetic to make it look
inflamed add fake blood to the center
and do keep in mind this is going to
look pretty gory so here's the final
result thank you so much for watching